boxedart.com 2013-08-05

# 

BOXEDART.COM PRIVACY POLICY.
This site is owned and operated by Big Resources, Inc., the parent company of
BoxedArt.com. For personal information protection purposes, BoxedArt.com and Big
Resources, Inc. are the controllers and, unless otherwise noted, are also the
processors of the personal information.
This Policy governs the information we collect about you and your use of information
we provide to you. By accepting this Policy and the Website Terms of Access
Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal
information in a manner prescribed in this Policy. You acknowledge this by using the
Site. Information collected may be retained for as long as it is reasonably required
for the purposes it was collected.
At BoxedArt.com and Big Resources, Inc. we care about providing you with tools and
information to manage and protect your online privacy. We have developed this
Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as "Policy") to inform you about how we deal
with privacy issues in relation to our website, what information this web site collects,
who may receive that information, what we may do with the information, and how
long we keep it. This Policy governs the information we collect about you and your
use of information we provide to you. By accepting this Policy and the Website
Terms of Access Agreement, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your
personal information in a manner prescribed in this Policy. You acknowledge this by
using the Site.
While we have made every attempt to make this policy as clear as possible, if you
have any further questions about it, please contact us:
Big Resources, Inc.
PO Box 46175
Tampa, FL 33646
Support: https://www.boxedart.com/support/index.php
Corporate Headquarters: (812) 762-4251
Does    this   website    use    cookies   to   keep   track   of  my   information?
Yes, this website uses cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your
hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information, that can
later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The
information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your
registration information, session identification number and your navigational history
and preferences.
In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We
have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the
use of cookies by BoxedArt.com and Big Resources, Inc. only, and does not cover the
use of cookies by third parties.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept
cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you
choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive
features of our sites and services that depend on cookies but you will be able to
perform basic navigation through the site.
                                            1

What types of information does this website collect?
We only collect personal information about you after you have provided us with your
consent to collect that specific information. By voluntarily providing this information
to us, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information as set out
in this privacy policy.
1.      NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION. We collect the following types of non-
        personal information and navigational information, which may be collected
        automatically as part of the site's operation:
       Information about the user's computer system, such as the web browser type
        and language, IP address, internet service provider, and operating system;
       The website that referred you to us and access times;
       Information about the pages you view;
       The links you click;
       The number of times you visit our site in a month;
       The size of the files you look at; and
       Other actions taken in connection with the site.
       Demographic information (i.e. your occupation, hobbies, gender, or interests)
        may be collected and linked to your personal information.
2.      PERSONAL INFORMATION. Personal information that we collect may
        include the following:
       Traditional contact information such as mailing address, phone number, and
        fax number;
       Internet contact information such email addresses;
       Information collected when you make a purchase, including your billing
        address.
       Non-financial identification information, such as your member username and
        password combination.
    NOTE: You may elect not to provide certain personal information, but doing so
    may limit, or otherwise make unavailable, certain products and/or services to
    you.
Why is this website collecting the information?
We collect the information for the following purposes:
       To complete the current activity of the visitor;
       To create and manage your membership account;
       To process your transactions;
       To provide customer service;
       For website administration purposes.
       To evaluate, review, or improve the website, products, services, and
        technologies offered;
       To notify visitors of updates to the sites, and/or contact them to market
        products or services;
       To run contests, select entrants, and choose prize winners;
                                             2

       To run Interactive Areas;
       To monitor who is accessing the membership section of BoxedArt.com or
        using the services offered on the website;
       To create a profile of the general audience accessing BoxedArt.com; and
       To communicate with you about your transaction.
    We may send transaction-related communications to you such as welcome
    letters, billing reminders, expiration notifications, and purchase confirmations.
    We may also send you surveys, newsletters, product updates, or marketing
    communications, or offers that may be of interest. If you do not wish to receive
    certain website notifications and announcements, you may make this election by
    logging into your account and updating your notification preferences accordingly
    or follow the unsubscribe instructions that are detailed within the email
    notifications. Please keep in mind, however, if you choose not to receive
    marketing communications or site announcements and updates, you will continue
    to receive transactional or account communications.
    Personal information collected by BoxedArt.com and/or Big Resources, Inc. may
    be stored and processed in the United States of America or any other country in
    which BoxedArt.com, Big Resources, Inc., their affiliates, subsidiaries, or other
    agents maintain facilities, and by providing us with your personal information and
    using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information
    outside of your country.
Who will receive the information? Except as set out in this privacy policy,
BoxedArt.com does not disclose or sell your personal information to any third-
parties.    Please review the possible and defined disclosures of your personal
information below:
1.      We may disclose your personal information to third-party service providers
        who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may hire other
        companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to
        host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in marketing, to
        conduct audits, etc. Those third-party service providers (i) shall be permitted
        to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service, (ii)
        must protect personal information to the same extent as BoxedArt.com and
        Big Resources, Inc., and (iii) shall be prohibited from using it for any other
        purpose.
2.      Information about our customers, including personal information, may be
        disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its
        assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or
        receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the
        business assets of the company. We will notify you of such an occurrence as
        described in the "Changes to This Privacy Policy" section below. We reserve
        the right to disclose your personal information if required or permitted to do
        so by law.
3.      The information will be shared with the following parties:
               Our internal staff and our direct agents.
                                             3

How long will the information be kept?
Information collected may be retained for as long as it is reasonably required for the
purposes it was collected. Session data expires at the end of a visit. Logged data is
reviewed for errors, and rotated frequently. Member data is stored for long term
customer service purposes.
How can I access and review my personal information?
If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us,
you may access and change your personal information by logging into your account
and clicking "Account Details". You may also contact our customer service
department directly by clicking the "Support" tab located within the top navigation
on all pages of the website.
What if I think there are inaccuracies in my information?
If you believe we are not handling your information in accordance with our privacy
policy, please contact our customer service department. Contact information is
available at https://www.boxedart.com/support/index.php.
If for some reason we have violated our privacy policy, we will correct the error as
soon as you notify us.
How is my personal information securely retained?
We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal
information, including without limitation:
              Limiting access to your personal information to those employees or
               personnel that require it to provide services to you;
              Requiring employees or personnel to sign confidentiality agreements to
               protect customer and other confidential information;
              Ensuring that third-part service providers sign confidentiality
               agreements to maintain the confidentiality of your personal
               information and not to use it for any unauthorized purposes;
              Encrypting credit card information on our order forms using secure
               socket layer (SSL) technology; and
              Storing your personal information in secure computer systems which
               protect it from unauthorized access or use.
Of course, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic
storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal
information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If a password is used to
protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your
password confidential at all times.
Forums & Other Interactive Services
Our sites may include discussion forums or other interactive areas or services,
including blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards, message boards, online hosting or
storage services, or other areas or services in which you or third parties create, post
or store any content, messages, comments, materials or other items on the sites
                                            4

("Interactive Areas"). If you use an Interactive Area, you should be aware that
these areas are open to the public and any personal information you post or provide
at registration may be viewable by others. We are not responsible for personal
information you submit in connection with the Interactive Areas, nor are we
responsible for how others might use that information, including to send you
unsolicited messages. Interactive Area postings may be retained indefinitely. If at
any time you would like to inquire about a posting, please contact us using the
method outlined within the designated forum or Interactive Area where such post
was made. Keep in mind that removal of a posting from an Interactive Area does not
mean that the posting will be deleted from our systems.
Email Referrals
If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or
services, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will use that
information to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site
and review the product or service you have selected.
Information about Children
Children (persons under the age of 18 years) are not eligible to use our services
unsupervised and we ask that children not submit any personal information to us.
We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age
of 18 without parental consent. If you are under 18, you shall not use or enter
information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site
without parental consent. If you are under the age of 18 years, you can browse the
Site only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians.
If you are under 18 years of age you cannot use the Membership Section of the Site.
It is the responsibility of parents to monitor their children's use of our Site.
Disclaimer/Links
BoxedArt.com contains links to other sites that have different privacy policies and
practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or
practices of such linked sites. BoxedArt.com strongly recommends that you read the
privacy policies of the linked websites as they may contain further terms and
conditions which apply to you.
Modifications or Updates to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to change the terms of this Policy at any time. Such changes
will be effective when a notice of the change is made available on the website. If
there are material changes to this statement or in how BoxedArt.com will use your
personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting a notice of such
changes here or on our home page, or by sending you an email. We encourage you
to review this policy whenever you visit BoxedArt.com or any properties held by
BoxedArt.com or Big Resources, Inc. respectively.
                                             5
